// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
const questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who found Diariong Tagalog?",
    answer: "Marcelo del Pilar",
    options: [
      "Juan Luna",
      "Marcelo del Pilar",
      "Pedro Laktaw",
      "Gregorio Sanciano"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Taga-Ilog was the pen name which was associated with:",
    answer: "Antonio Luna",
    options: [
      "Juan Luna",
      "Mariano Ponce",
      "Jose Ma. Panganiban",
      "Antonio Luna"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The political section of the Asociacion Hispano-Filipino was under the charge of:",
    answer: "Marcelo del Pilar",
    options: [
      "Jose Rizal",
      "Marcelo del Pilar",
      "Dominador Gomez",
      "Thomas Arejola"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of these is not true of the La Solidaridad?",
    answer: "It featured articles about the good deeds of the friars.",
    options: [
      "It was a forum for discussion of the issues concerning the Philippines.",
      "It was the official organ of the reform movement.",
      "It was a vehicle for the expression of the political views of the reformers.",
      "It featured articles about the good deeds of the friars."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What did The First Philippine Republic came to be called?",
    answer: "Malolos Republic",
    options: [
      "Biak-na-Bato Republic",
      "Sakay Republic",
      "Malolos Republic",
      "Non of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Because of which reason, was Rizal not in favor of the revolution planned by the Katipunan?",
    answer: "Unpreparedness of the Katipuneros for an armed struggle",
    options: [
      "Unpreparedness of the Katipuneros for an armed struggle",
      "Willingness to the wealthy Filipinos to support the struggle",
      "Absence of a military tactician who will direct the military operations of the KKK",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Based on the plan proposed by whom was The Malolos Constitution drafted? ",
    answer: "Calderon",
    options: [
      "Paterno",
      "Calderon",
      "Mabini",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What was The rightist wing of La Liga called?",
    answer: "Cuerpos de Compromisarios",
    options: [
      "Cuerpos de Propagandistas",
      "Cuerpos de Compromisarios",
      "Cuerpos de Militantes",
      "Cuerpos de la Revolucionarios"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Tell the name of the president of the Associacion La Solidaridad.",
    answer: "Galiciano Apacible",
    options: [
      "Galiciano Apacible",
      "Mariano Ponce",
      "Manuel Sta. Maria",
      "Jose Ma. Panganiban"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The first real battle fought between Filipinos and the Spaniards is known as:",
    answer: "Pinaglabanan",
    options: [
      "Majayjay",
      "Pugad Lawin",
      "Pinaglabanan",
      "Montalban"
    ]
  },
];